<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/recent/</link><title>Recent Announcements</title><description>The AWS Cloud platform expands daily. Learn about announcements, launches, news, innovation and more from Amazon Web Services.</description><managingEditor>aws@amazon.com (Amazon Web Services)</managingEditor><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:47:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><image><url>https://a0.awsstatic.com/main/images/logos/aws_logo_smile_179x109.png</url><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/recent/</link><title>Recent Announcements</title><description>The AWS Cloud platform expands daily. Learn about announcements, launches, news, innovation and more from Amazon Web Services.</description></image><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-cloudformation-changesets-enhanced-change-visibility-deployments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47c946538bf92b96ef9fddcfc8ca089741ccfa89</guid><title>AWS CloudFormation ChangeSets now offer enhanced change visibility for deployments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CloudFormation enhances &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/using-cfn-updating-stacks-changesets.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ChangeSets&lt;/a&gt; to&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;provide a detailed preview of the actions that CloudFormation will take in a deployment. This launch helps improve your ability to assess whether a deployment will cause unintended changes to running resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:51:41 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-cloudformation,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cognito-europe-spain-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3070bd4916adb6de37212d8e3e283680878fd071</guid><title>Amazon Cognito is now available in Europe (Spain) Region </title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Cognito is now available in Europe (Spain) Region. Amazon Cognito makes it easy to add authentication, authorization, and user management to your web and mobile apps. Amazon Cognito scales to millions of users and supports sign-in with social identity providers such as Apple, Facebook, Google, and Amazon, and enterprise identity providers via standards such as SAML 2.0 and OpenID Connect.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 20:36:55 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cognito,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/monitor-internet-outage-weather-map-cloudwatch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">be4d4793438f6f77364c73ca06f859ee3df4dba0</guid><title>Monitor internet outage using the weather map in CloudWatch Internet Monitor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;All AWS customers who navigate to Amazon CloudWatch Internet Monitor console can now view the internet weather map, at no charge, which shares a 24-hour global snapshot of internet latency and availability outages. The map lets you see, at a glance, recent internet issues across the world, including specific cities and service providers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-network-manager-israel-tel-aviv-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4f32a0cff2b4fd797fe19c4fc217e388c6f32048</guid><title>AWS Network Manager is now available in AWS Israel (Tel Aviv) Region </title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, AWS Network Manager is available in the AWS Israel (Tel Aviv) Region. AWS Network Manager reduces the operational complexity of managing global networks across AWS and on-premises locations. It provides a single global view of your private network. You can visualize your global network in a topology diagram and monitor your network using CloudWatch Metrics and Events for network topology changes, routing updates, and connection status updates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 20:04:39 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/transit-gateway-network-manager,marketing:marchitecture/networking-and-content-delivery</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-athena-federated-query-pass-through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ed8064067d59f930daca35b80e038b7fb53783f</guid><title>Amazon Athena announces federated query pass-through</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="/athena/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Athena&lt;/a&gt; announced&amp;nbsp;federated query pass-through, a new feature that allows entire queries to be executed directly on the underlying data source. Federated query pass-through allows you to take advantage of the unique functions, query language, and performance capabilities of different data sources, and can result in faster query execution and less data processed by Athena.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-athena,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cognito-asia-pacific-hyderabad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">874e09172351cc6c3ab8fd78a701287b2dc2a21b</guid><title>Amazon Cognito is now available in Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) </title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Cognito is now available in Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) Region. Amazon Cognito makes it easy to add authentication, authorization, and user management to your web and mobile apps. Amazon Cognito scales to millions of users and supports sign-in with social identity providers such as Apple, Facebook, Google, and Amazon, and enterprise identity providers via standards such as SAML 2.0 and OpenID Connect.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 20:35:45 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cognito,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-mwaa-larger-environment-sizes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1f3569461bbfbcd31b9fe6765f7ae835a465ba3f</guid><title>Amazon MWAA adds larger environment sizes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA) now offers larger environment sizes, giving customers of the managed service the ability to define a greater number of workflows in each Apache Airflow environment, supporting more complex tasks that can utilize increased resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 19:24:25 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-mwaa,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-corretto-april-2024-quarterly-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32893ba4f58f82fbb06adad1de34c2e5b49318e2</guid><title>Amazon Corretto April, 2024 quarterly updates</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On April 16, 2024 Amazon announced quarterly security and critical updates for Amazon Corretto Long-Term Supported (LTS) and Feature Release (FR) versions of OpenJDK. Corretto 22.0.1, 21.0.3, 17.0.11, 11.0.23, 8u412 are now available for download. Amazon Corretto is a no-cost, multi-platform, production-ready distribution of OpenJDK.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 20:27:44 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-corretto,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-well-architected-tool-connector-jira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">bb1f131de0f3c207bcaba3d71c7445c128d0cc3b</guid><title>Announcing the AWS Well-Architected Tool Connector for Jira</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS Well-Architected introduces a new connector for Jira, which helps you create a closed-loop mechanism to efficiently manage and track your risks over time. You can now configure the Well-Architected Tool to generate Jira tickets and send updates directly to the Well-Architected Tool as tickets are resolved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 19:03:39 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-well-architected-tool,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/anthropics-claude-3-opus-amazon-bedrock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">85bba4e5e7128c0641795871f1c19eba0b791061</guid><title>Anthropic's Claude 3 Opus model now available on Amazon Bedrock</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropic’s Claude 3 Opus foundation model, the most advanced and intelligent model in the Claude 3 Family, is now available on &lt;a href="/bedrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt;. The Claude 3 family of models (Claude 3 Opus, Claude 3 Sonnet, and Claude 3 Haiku) is the next generation of state-of-the-art models from Anthropic. Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed service that offers a choice of high-performing foundation models from leading AI companies, like Anthropic, along with a broad set of capabilities that provide you with the easiest way to build and scale generative AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:02:05 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-oracle-oracle-apex-version-23-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a3d6172bbfc6a40097b2f251f38d39a03c726397</guid><title>Amazon RDS for Oracle now supports Oracle Application Express (APEX) Version 23.2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/oracle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) for Oracle&lt;/a&gt; now supports version 23.2 of Oracle Application Express (APEX) for 19c and 21c versions of Oracle Database. Using APEX, developers can build applications entirely within their web browser.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-rds-for-oracle</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-oracle-data-guard-switchover-automated-backups-additional-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a1c32962fd8af4eb5acff5d1b87cac66523b6c60</guid><title>Amazon RDS for Oracle supports managed Oracle Data Guard Switchover and Automated Backups for replicas in additional regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/oracle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon RDS for Oracle&lt;/a&gt; now supports additional regions for Oracle Data Guard Switchover and Automated Backups of replica instances (read-only and mounted) deployed within an Availability Zone, or in separate Availability Zones of a given Region, or in separate AWS Regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds-for-oracle,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-sql-server-minor-version-2022-cu12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ab93bba51cba08037ded86a2f5906eee9facff1</guid><title>Amazon RDS for SQL supports minor version 2022 CU12</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A new minor version of Microsoft SQL Server is now available on &lt;a href="/rds/sqlserver/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon RDS for SQL Server&lt;/a&gt;, providing performance enhancements and security fixes. Amazon RDS for SQL Server now supports the latest minor version of SQL Server 2022 across the Express, Web, Standard, and Enterprise editions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:11:35 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-rds-for-sql-server,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-custom-oracle-database-standard-edition-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4fad67a4495448cb96187e9584bb4ee1a7f2d4fb</guid><title>Amazon RDS Custom for Oracle now supports Oracle Database Standard Edition 2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/custom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) Custom&lt;/a&gt; for Oracle, a managed database service for legacy, custom, and packaged applications that require access to the underlying operating system and database environment, now supports Oracle Database Standard Edition 2 (SE2). &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds-for-oracle,general:products/amazon-rds,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-msk-canada-west-calgary-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8417d67b2c0fc0873878b99a41938522f7fbc324</guid><title>Amazon MSK is now available in Canada West (Calgary) Region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (&lt;a href="/msk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon MSK&lt;/a&gt;) is now available in Canada West(Calgary) Region. Amazon MSK is a fully managed service for Apache Kafka and Kafka Connect that makes it easier for you to build and run applications that use Apache Kafka as a data store. Amazon MSK is fully compatible with Apache Kafka, which enables you to more quickly migrate your existing Apache Kafka workloads to Amazon MSK with confidence or build new ones from scratch. With Amazon MSK, you spend more time building innovative streaming applications and less time managing Kafka clusters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-msk,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-oracle-x2iedn-additional-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4e3ff63ad1d1b7ce68796bfb5d52ffca79287cb9</guid><title>Amazon RDS for Oracle extends support for x2iedn in additional AWS regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/oracle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for Oracle&lt;/a&gt; now offers memory optimized X2iedn instances in Asia Pacific (Hyderabad, Jakarta and Osaka), Europe (Milan and Paris), US West (N. California), AWS GovCloud (US-East) and AWS GovCloud (US-West).&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:54:01 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds-for-oracle,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-quicksight-account-instances-iam-identity-center/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">85da0e0099541609ba89dfd3ded58ae465167e42</guid><title>Amazon QuickSight now supports account instances of IAM Identity Center</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/quicksight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon QuickSight&lt;/a&gt; now supports account instances of IAM Identity Center when creating a new subscription to QuickSight. Administrators can sign up for QuickSight and choose an account instance of IAM Identity Center that exists in the same AWS account as their QuickSight subscription. Account instances support isolated deployments of applications in a single AWS account, leveraging IAM Identity Center workforce identity and access portal features. Account instances are bound to a single AWS account and are used only to manage user and group access for applications in the same account and AWS region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-quicksight,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-healthomics-reading-sequence-stores-s3-apis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">17089d1b5088a4871de7c9aaec01fe8040a4af44</guid><title>AWS HealthOmics announces support for reading sequence stores through Amazon S3 APIs</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce &lt;a href="/healthomics/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS HealthOmics&lt;/a&gt; now&amp;nbsp;supports reading sequence store objects using Amazon S3 APIs. AWS HealthOmics is a fully managed service that empowers healthcare and life science organizations to store, query, analyze omics data, and generate insights to improve health and drive scientific discoveries. With this release, customers can more easily integrate HealthOmics data stores into their bioinformatics ecosystem while benefiting from the domain-specific metadata, cost-savings, and scalability.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:58:03 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-health,general:products/amazon-omics,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-privatelink-supports-quicksight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f4f14bc43e3e5a98e305bc04483d78dc71993ac1</guid><title>AWS PrivateLink now supports Amazon QuickSight</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/privatelink/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS PrivateLink&lt;/a&gt; now supports &lt;a href="/quicksight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon QuickSight&lt;/a&gt;, providing private connectivity between the QuickSight website, virtual private clouds (VPCs) or on-premises networks without exposing traffic to the public internet. With this integration, administrators can also use VPC endpoint policies to restrict access to QuickSight accounts that are not authorized on their network.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-privatelink,general:products/amazon-quicksight,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/networking-and-content-delivery,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-kms-automatic-key-rotation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fe15da89df9a6b859b6fa2376c9e2f8c57f64da7</guid><title>AWS KMS announces more flexible automatic key rotation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="/kms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;announces&amp;nbsp;new flexibility, visibility, and pricing for automatic key rotation. You can now customize the frequency of rotation period between 90 days to 7 years (2560 days) as well as invoke key rotation on demand for customer managed KMS keys. Lastly, you can now see the history of all previous rotations for any KMS key that has been rotated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:50:51 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-kms,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-resource-explorer-additional-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3271ffc2bdc1f1f49f4a04b71ffaa9af8e4de16d</guid><title>AWS Resource Explorer is now available in 10 additional AWS Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS Resource Explorer has expanded the availability of resource search and discovery to 10 additional AWS Regions: Africa (Cape Town), Middle East (UAE), Asia Pacific (Hong Kong), Asia Pacific (Hyderabad), Asia Pacific (Melbourne), Europe (Milan), Israel (Tel Aviv), Canada West (Calgary), Europe (Spain), and Europe (Zurich). With this launch, customers can turn on Resource Explorer to search for and discover resources across all commercial AWS Regions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:30:18 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-resource-explorer,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-step-functions-integration-elemental-mediaconvert/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">459cd91e77b4526c1ec615405e76b5be3eeddbf3</guid><title>AWS Step Functions Announces Optimized Integration for AWS Elemental MediaConvert</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/step-functions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Step Functions&lt;/a&gt; announces an optimized integration for &lt;a href="/mediaconvert/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Elemental MediaConvert&lt;/a&gt;, enabling video transcode jobs in your workflow. With this integration, customers can easily build automated, resilient media workflows using the visual authoring and operator experience of Step Functions. With the new Run a Job (.sync) integration pattern for the MediaConvert CreateJob API, Step Functions will wait for asynchronous MediaConvert transcoding jobs to complete before progressing to the next step, simplifying the orchestration of multi-step media processing pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:14:59 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-step-functions,marketing:marchitecture/media-services,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-detective-investigations-guardduty-monitoring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d5a7cf294f51f97c0324d71581a04c526f6ce856</guid><title>Amazon Detective supports investigations for GuardDuty EC2 Runtime Monitoring </title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Detective, a managed security service that helps analysts investigate potential security issues across AWS, has introduced a new feature to support investigating threats detected by Amazon GuardDuty's EC2 Runtime Monitoring capability. This expansion enhances Detective's ability to provide visualizations and context for investigating runtime threats targeting EC2 instances.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:37:15 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-detective,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-elemental-mediatailor-hls-interstitials-vod-streams/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">df817fd08b32a2bbf0c651f37065b78edc98be01</guid><title>AWS Elemental MediaTailor now supports HLS Interstitials for VOD streams</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, AWS Elemental MediaTailor now supports HLS Interstitials for video-on-demand (VOD) streams. This feature, which you can enable as an option, automatically conditions manifests so ad break pods are decoupled from the main content stream. By separating the ad content from the main video stream, HLS Interstitials provides more efficient ad payload delivery reducing video start-up time when compared to traditional Server-Side Ad Insertion and reduced buffering or errors during ad breaks compared to Client-Side Ad Insertion.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-elemental-mediatailor,marketing:marchitecture/media-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-transfer-family-tls-certificates-3des-as2-messages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">849a28426894fe2fcc3e296944e521999e4a4aca</guid><title>AWS Transfer Family supports self-signed TLS certificates, 3DES encryption for sending AS2 messages</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Transfer Family now provides you with the option to import and use a trading partner’s public, self-signed TLS certificate for sending Applicability Statement 2 (AS2) messages to their server over HTTPS. Additionally, you can now choose to encrypt messages sent to your partner’s server using the 3DES cipher. By default, AS2 connectors will encrypt messages with the AES128 cipher unless you select 3DES for purposes of backwards compatibility with your partner’s existing AS2 implementation. These capabilities add to AWS Transfer Family’s existing list of AS2 interoperability features and enable you to reliably connect with trading partners that require these specific security configurations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:00:55 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-transfer-family,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-braket-experimental-capabilities-quera-device-braket-direct/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d5e99afcdedb15c2bac0e126dddc9019fea2844a</guid><title>Amazon Braket adds experimental capabilities for QuEra device via Braket Direct</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/braket/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Braket&lt;/a&gt; now provides access to three new experimental capabilities via Braket Direct, offering increased flexibility and control when programming on QuEra’s Aquila device. With today’s launch, you can get access to local detuning, taller geometries, and tighter geometries - opening up new research opportunities, such as advanced combinatorial optimization problems that are relevant for various industry applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 21:22:30 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-braket,marketing:marchitecture/quantum-technologies</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/workflow-monitor-aws-media-services/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1f61724dd11a82a845130e9c36f6603856bcb030</guid><title>Introducing workflow monitor for AWS Media Services</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the release of workflow monitor for live video, a media-centric tool to simplify and elevate the monitoring of your video workloads. Accessible via the &lt;a href="/medialive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Elemental MediaLive&lt;/a&gt; console and API, workflow monitor discovers and visualizes resources. It creates signal maps showing video across AWS Elemental MediaConnect, MediaLive, and MediaPackage along with Amazon S3 and Amazon CloudFront to provide end-to-end visibility. With the workflow monitor, you can create your own alarm templates or start from a set of recommended alarms, and build custom templates for alarm notifications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 19:31:29 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/media-services,general:products/aws-elemental-medialive</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-healthimaging-search-parameters-api-responses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">303c3a018e718a922addd7aa34eacd0d281e92fc</guid><title>AWS HealthImaging adds search parameters and extended search API responses</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS HealthImaging has upgraded its search functionality so that customers can more easily find and access their medical imaging data in the cloud. These enhancements simplify finding any patient exam, for use as a clinical prior, to inform a clinical workflow, or for processing by medical imaging AI/ML models. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:59:35 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-healthimaging,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-neuron-speculative-decoding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">39141c49b2df36a29f823a49d1f5552db9688e72</guid><title>AWS Neuron introduces speculative decoding</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the release of Neuron 2.18, introducing stable support (out of beta) for PyTorch 2.1 and adding support for speculative decoding&amp;nbsp;with &lt;a href="https://github.com/aws-neuron/aws-neuron-samples/tree/master/torch-neuronx/transformers-neuronx/inference/speculative_sampling.ipynb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Llama-2-70B sample&lt;/a&gt; in Transformers NeuronX library.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-lambda-functions-12x-faster-govcloud-us-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4a7b3999fd0932163168cf13c62b37e6fb26825c</guid><title>AWS Lambda functions now scale up to 12X faster in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Lambda functions can now scale up to 12x faster than before in response to unpredictable traffic in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. With this improvement each function can scale up to a rate of 1,000 concurrent executions every 10 seconds, up to your account concurrency limit. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-lambda,marketing:marchitecture/serverless,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudfront-oac-aws-elemental-mediapackage-origin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">68c60b2d8a9fa4f26180173f9286d127833c611c</guid><title>Amazon CloudFront now supports Origin Access Control (OAC) for AWS Elemental MediaPackage Origin</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, customers can protect their AWS Elemental MediaPackage origins by using CloudFront Origin Access Control (OAC) to only allow access from designated CloudFront distributions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 22:02:26 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudfront,marketing:marchitecture/networking</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-emr-eks-simplified-access-management-controls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1ee34b5bbac1d2d8f076d88fac55b8f878f0c14c</guid><title>Amazon EMR on EKS now supports Amazon EKS simplified access management controls</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that Amazon EMR on EKS simplified the authentication and authorization user experience by integrating with &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/a-deep-dive-into-simplified-amazon-eks-access-management-controls/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon EKS's improved cluster access management controls&lt;/a&gt;. With this launch,&amp;nbsp;Amazon EMR on EKS will use EKS access management controls to automatically obtain the necessary permissions to run Amazon EMR applications on the EKS cluster.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 17:03:47 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-emr,general:products/amazon-eks,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/containers</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-iam-identity-center-shortcut-links-aws-access-portal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45d61f9b01a73d278e2f25ad856d32c70b761769</guid><title>AWS IAM Identity Center now offers a streamlined AWS access portal and shortcut links</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Users of AWS IAM Identity Center can now take advantage of a streamlined AWS access portal and time-saving shortcut links to navigate directly to destinations in the AWS Management Console in accordance with their permissions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 18:41:35 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-iam-identity-center,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudfront-oac-lambda-function-url-origins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">809ff3d6a37432c5a498a0546924c682a166478c</guid><title>Amazon CloudFront now supports Origin Access Control (OAC) for Lambda function URL origins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, customers can protect their AWS Lambda URL origins by using CloudFront Origin Access Control (OAC) to only allow access from designated CloudFront distributions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 22:07:31 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudfront,marketing:marchitecture/networking-and-content-delivery</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudwatch-container-insights-windows-containers-eks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">be4b20c3c083e193f0a056384f4eaaf01da99bc5</guid><title>Amazon CloudWatch Container Insights announces observability for Windows containers on Amazon EKS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon CloudWatch Container Insights now offers observability for Windows containers running on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS), and helps customers collect, aggregate, and summarize metrics and logs from their Windows container infrastructure. With this support, customers can monitor utilization of resources such as CPU, memory, disk, and network, as well as get enhanced observability such as container-level EKS performance metrics, Kube-state metrics and EKS control plane metrics for Windows containers. CloudWatch also provides diagnostic information, such as container restart failures, for faster problem isolation and troubleshooting for Windows containers running on EKS.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 17:05:45 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-verified-permissions-additional-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">08d5d847276d0da8232a7ac755e371381bd28cf4</guid><title>Amazon Verified Permissions is available in four additional regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Verified Permissions is now available in the AWS GovCloud (US-East) and (US-West) Regions, AWS Israel (Tel Aviv) and Canada West (Calgary). The service provides fine-grained authorization for the applications that you build, allowing you to implement permissions as policies rather than application code. Your application calls Verified Permissions to authorize access to APIs and resources managed by the application.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-clean-rooms-differential-privacy-generally-available/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b361e65c97e4b57395adddd524c57a29a58a449a</guid><title>AWS Clean Rooms Differential Privacy is now generally available</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the general availability of AWS Clean Rooms Differential Privacy, a new capability that helps you protect the privacy of your users with mathematically-backed and intuitive controls in just a few steps. As a fully managed capability, no prior differential privacy experience is needed to help you protect the privacy of your users.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:20:10 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-clean-rooms,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-location-service-tracking-sdk-ios-android/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">42abe66deeda03143272a82ca416386f47e147e2</guid><title>Amazon Location Service releases Tracking SDK for iOS and Android</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Location Service has released the Tracking SDK for iOS and Android platforms. Developers can now easily add location tracking capabilities into their mobile applications to support customer engagement, geo-targeting, and delivery use cases.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:53:54 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-location-service,marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-route-53-additional-top-level-domains/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ef8428be00386b14b5dbeb0f0035832d6adf121a</guid><title>Amazon Route 53 adds support for 18 additional Top-Level Domains</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Route 53 offers domain name registration services and provides easy integration with other AWS services. We are excited to announce the recent addition of 18 additional Top-Level Domains (TLDs) to the existing 351 that we already supported before this launch. You can now register domains with: .beer, .bid, .bio, .christmas, .contact, .design, .fan, .fun, .law, .llc, .ltd, .pw, .shopping, .ski, .software, .stream, .vote and .work. Common use cases for some of these new TLDs include the following:&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:59:44 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-route-53,marketing:marchitecture/networking</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-mysql-rds-superuser-role/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d2141d14a9f9eab78bf3535662a335af4bbf9314</guid><title>Amazon RDS for MySQL supports rds_superuser_role for easier implementation of role based privileges</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/mysql/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for MySQL&lt;/a&gt; now supports rds_superuser_role to simplify implementation of role-based privileges on MySQL 8.0. The rds_superuser_role is granted by default to the primary administrative user, and has privileges including, CREATE ROLE, CREATE USER, and DROP ROLE, for all database objects. For a complete list of rds_superuser_role privileges, refer to the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/MysQL.Concepts.UsersAndPrivileges.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:02:07 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds-for-mysql,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudfront-cmcd-fields-real-time-logs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7f5ed9a4f051767dbde188a8a01dcd766a8d91f2</guid><title>Amazon CloudFront now supports Common Media Client Data (CMCD) fields in real-time logs</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can enable Common Media Client Data (&lt;a href="https://cdn.cta.tech/cta/media/media/resources/standards/pdfs/cta-5004-final.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;CMCD&lt;/a&gt;) fields in your CloudFront real-time logs. You can select key client-side performance parameters and CloudFront delivery performance parameters in the same log record. This can help you correlate variations in Quality of Experience (QoE) for your viewers to CloudFront performance at the granularity of single viewer sessions, simplifying the troubleshooting of QoE issues that impact your viewers engagement.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudfront,marketing:marchitecture/media-services,marketing:marchitecture/networking</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-bedrock-sydney-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3cfd7682da89ff6b247cf74aae653ea61b0fb461</guid><title>Amazon Bedrock is now available in the Asia Pacific (Sydney) Region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, customers can use Amazon Bedrock in the Asia Pacific (Sydney) Region to easily build and scale generative AI applications using a variety of foundation models (FMs) as well as powerful tools to build generative AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 22:33:30 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-elemental-mediatailor-hyderabad-uae-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c3c6a2a85c3639a6695610d078772267f054d69c</guid><title>AWS Elemental MediaTailor now available in the Hyderabad and UAE regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now configure and operate AWS Elemental MediaTailor through the AWS Management Console or API endpoints in the Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) and Middle East (UAE) AWS Regions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-elemental-mediatailor,marketing:marchitecture/media-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-appsync-application-headers-lambda-authorizer-functions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5fca785e789a6e4df1224deea8bf23f8b92176bd</guid><title>AWS AppSync forwards application request headers to AWS Lambda custom authorizer functions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS AppSync is a fully managed service that enables developers to build digital experiences based on multiple data sources. With AppSync, you create GraphQL APIs that your applications interact with over the internet (public APIs) or inside your VPC (private APIs). A method of authorization is always required to access your AppSync API. Developers can chose from several authorization modes to authorize their requests based on their business requirements, including calling an AWS Lambda function to implement custom authorization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:55:31 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-appsync,marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/knowledge-bases-amazon-bedrock-claude-3-haiku/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">97c7bdad7a3cb7d0d7218d17f9c73c3e2c983c7c</guid><title>Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports Claude 3 Haiku</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock securely connects foundation models (FMs) to internal company data sources for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) to deliver more relevant and accurate responses. Anthropic’s Claude 3 Haiku foundation model is now generally available on Knowledge Bases. We recently also announced support for &lt;a href="/about-aws/whats-new/2024/03/knowledge-bases-amazon-bedrock-claude-3-sonnet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Claude 3 Sonnet&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/availability-aws-outposts-kingdom-saudi-arabia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fb730639470effcfc0570504af8f8d2f2ac874a0</guid><title>Announcing availability of AWS Outposts in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Outposts can be shipped and installed at customer datacenters and on-premises locations in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:34:36 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-outposts</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-elemental-medialive-cmaf-ingest-output-group/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05dc769c2b75f282cf0e93e2700022cf07d5d5f0</guid><title>AWS Elemental MediaLive now supports CMAF Ingest output group</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now use &lt;a href="/medialive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Elemental MediaLive&lt;/a&gt; to deliver a &lt;a href="https://dashif-documents.azurewebsites.net/Ingest/master/DASH-IF-Ingest.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;CMAF Ingest&lt;/a&gt; (Interface-1) output group from a channel.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:21:29 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/media-services,general:products/aws-elemental-medialive</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-transfer-family-workshop-sftp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ab9356989b9b553a04a8b72b4a7e8551ccaa3b8a</guid><title>AWS Transfer Family introduces a new workshop for SFTP</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now learn how to use AWS Transfer Family to set up your SFTP endpoint, manage your line-of-business users, and enable secure access to your data with a new workshop called Basic principles for securing access using AWS Transfer Family. This workshop will help you gain hands on experience so you can build a scalable and secure file transfer architecture on AWS without needing to modify existing applications or manage server infrastructure. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-transfer-family,marketing:marchitecture/migration</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-india-customers-upi-make-payments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">97ca6e34dc3648a245537cbc338e3a7d631bf7dd</guid><title>AWS India customers can now use UPI (Unified Payments Interface) to make payments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS India customers can now pay their invoices using &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/edit-aispl-payment-method.html#using-unified-payment-interface-for-payments" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;UPI (Unified Payments Interface) payment method&lt;/a&gt;, in addition to credit cards, debit cards, and netbanking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:21:56 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-account-billing</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudwatch-rum-additional-aws-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8b64ab561bcd8b5cb05975d742719bb1665f4b56</guid><title>Amazon CloudWatch RUM is generally available in 11 additional AWS Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon CloudWatch RUM, which enables customers to monitor their web applications by collecting client side performance and error data in real time, is generally available in the following 11 AWS Regions starting today: Africa (Cape Town), Asia Pacific (Jakarta), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Asia Pacific (Osaka), Asia Pacific (Seoul), Canada (Central), Europe (Milan), Europe (Paris), Middle East (Bahrain), South America (Sao Paulo), and US West (N. California).&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-opensearch-service-update-node-count-without-blue-green/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c084f1c967557323f9124fdd704c94d79729bdfa</guid><title>Amazon OpenSearch Service now lets you update node count without blue/green</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/latest/developerguide/createupdatedomains.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon OpenSearch Service&lt;/a&gt; is now extending the ability to update the number of data nodes without requiring a blue/green deployment for clusters without dedicated cluster manager (master) nodes. This change will allow you to make node count changes faster. Clusters with dedicated cluster manager nodes already supported updating the data node count without a blue/green deployment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-opensearch-service,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/storage</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-lambda-kafka-event-sources-four-new-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f0ccca672ff852ef17b9f8ed2021988d7400a6df</guid><title>AWS Lambda supports Kafka event sources in four new regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/lambda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/a&gt; now supports Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (MSK) and self-managed Apache Kafka as event sources in the Asia Pacific (Hyderabad), Asia Pacific (Melbourne), Europe (Spain), Europe (Zurich) Regions, enabling customers to build serverless applications that process streaming data from Kafka event sources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-lambda,marketing:marchitecture/compute,marketing:marchitecture/serverless</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-ec2-c7i-instances-europe-paris/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7338c94862f1eeacb5f344d6b3152f831018f5e1</guid><title>Amazon EC2 C7i instances now available in Europe (Paris)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7i instances powered by custom 4th Gen Intel Xeon Scalable processors (code-named Sapphire Rapids) are available in Europe (Paris). C7i instances supported by custom Intel processors, available only on AWS, offer up to 15% better performance over comparable x86-based Intel processors utilized by other cloud providers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 21:46:06 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudwatch-internet-monitor-cloudfront-console/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c6d702ed221d14eb8ef4fea94f89c8f1f9c3e3d7</guid><title>Launch Amazon CloudWatch Internet Monitor from Amazon CloudFront console</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now create or associate a monitor for a distribution directly from the Amazon CloudFront console. By adding your distribution to a monitor, you can gain improved visibility into your application's internet performance and availability using Amazon CloudWatch Internet Monitor. You can create a monitor for the distribution, or add the distribution to an existing monitor, directly from the distribution metrics dashboard on the CloudFront console. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:43:38 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,general:products/amazon-cloudfront,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,marketing:marchitecture/networking</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/knowledge-bases-amazon-bedrock-formation-quotas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">10a6709963147c3dac3dc7009f18d4313d9a8a5f</guid><title>Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock offers support for CloudFormation and Service Quotas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/bedrock/knowledge-bases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Knowledge Bases&lt;/a&gt; for Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) capability that allows you to connect foundation models (FMs) to internal company data sources to deliver relevant and accurate responses. We are excited to add new capabilities for building enterprise-ready RAG. Knowledge Bases now supports AWS CloudFormation and Service Quotas.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cognito-customers-access-apis-verified-permissions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c9471197dc627b9a17ecf9ca98f7b448e14f2120</guid><title>Amazon Cognito customers can secure access to APIs using Amazon Verified Permissions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS has launched a feature for Amazon Cognito customers to reduce the time spent securing Amazon API Gateway APIs with fine-grained access control, from weeks to days. The feature leverages Amazon Verified Permissions to manage and evaluate granular security policies that reference user attributes and groups. With a few clicks, you can enforce that only users in authorized Amazon Cognito groups have access to the application’s APIs. For example, say you are building a loan processing application, you can secure your application by restricting access to the “approve_loan” API to users in the “loan_officers” group. You can implement more fine-grained authorization, without making any code changes, by updating the underlying Cedar policy, so that only “loan_officers” above “Director” level can approve loans.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:02:54 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cognito,general:products/aws-verified-access,general:products/amazon-api-gateway</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-vpc-cni-automatic-subnet-discovery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9e243b5dd4c3f7840505cfc9b89468a0277fdbef</guid><title>Amazon VPC CNI now supports automatic subnet discovery</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now leverage tag-based subnet discovery capability of &lt;a href="https://github.com/aws/amazon-vpc-cni-k8s" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon VPC CNI&lt;/a&gt; to scale Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) clusters in IPv4 address space without adding operational complexity. In this new default mode, Kubernetes Pod IP addresses are allocated from all tagged and available subnets in your Amazon Virtual Private Cloud(VPC). &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:05:44 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-eks,marketing:marchitecture/containers</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cognito-asia-pacific-melbourne-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44c3fab3a66ab032276db2b5f3c9d6dc0b982714</guid><title>Amazon Cognito is now available in Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, customers can use Amazon Cognito in Asia Pacific (Melbourne) Region. Amazon Cognito makes it easy to add authentication, authorization, and user management to your web and mobile apps. Amazon Cognito scales to millions of users and supports sign-in with social identity providers such as Apple, Facebook, Google, and Amazon, and enterprise identity providers via standards such as SAML 2.0 and OpenID Connect.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:19:40 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cognito,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/research-engineering-studio-aws-version-2024-04-available/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7f1334761a5271b73106442a524ef95aae799c9a</guid><title>Research and Engineering Studio on AWS Version 2024.04 now available</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we’re excited to announce the release of Research and Engineering Studio (RES) on AWS Version 2024.04. This latest release brings new customization options for RES virtual desktops along with new options for shared storage and virtual desktop infrastructure (VDI) streaming.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:38:35 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-codecatalyst-tasks-issues/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">490dcdfea690cb5ebfa5438d542b50e6575db607</guid><title>Amazon CodeCatalyst now supports adding tasks to issues</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces that CodeCatalyst Issues now support breaking down issues into smaller units called tasks. CodeCatalyst customers can now add up to 100 tasks within a single issue to further organize and plan out the work involved. Tasks can be added when creating a new issue or later added to existing issues and can be assigned to any of the project members. You can also reorder, mark as complete, or remove tasks on an issue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-codecatalyst,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-ivs-low-latency-streaming-srt-ingest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fa5d0bb8cf4bdda482978f1e174444c0eead72a3</guid><title>Amazon IVS Low-Latency Streaming now supports SRT ingest</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can use the Secure Reliable Transport (SRT) protocol to broadcast to your Amazon Interactive Video Service (Amazon IVS) channels. This new protocol, in addition to RTMPS, expands options for live streaming and helps to maintain video quality when sent across varying network conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:42:51 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-ivs,marketing:marchitecture/media-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-transfer-family-workshop-file-transfer-sftp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ddaf5554929729b8c49a550a12ae3abc41bae2bd</guid><title>Announcing AWS Transfer Family workshop for building secure file transfer solutions using SFTP</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Transfer Family now provides an interactive workshop for building file transfer solutions using Secure File Transfer Protocol (SFTP). With this workshop in AWS Workshop Studio, you can learn how to build secure and automated business-to-business file transfer workflows in AWS, and integrate data from remote business partners in your applications and data lakes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:59:45 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-transfer-family,marketing:marchitecture/migration</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudwatch-tagging-alarms-cloudformation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ece8b2d3f059398e95de6ed81e7839533c31050d</guid><title>Amazon CloudWatch now supports tagging alarms with AWS CloudFormation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/cloudwatch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon CloudWatch&lt;/a&gt; now supports using &lt;a href="/cloudformation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS CloudFormation&lt;/a&gt; to manage tags when you create, update, or delete alarms.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:21:35 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/cross-account-observability-cloudwatch-internet-monitor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63eb315c987b6f729b956dfe6522e9a89139758e</guid><title>Cross-account observability enabled for CloudWatch Internet Monitor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now set up cross-account observability for Amazon CloudWatch Internet Monitor, so that you can get read-only access to monitors from multiple accounts within an AWS Region. Deploying applications by using resources in separate accounts is a good practice, to establish security and billing boundaries between teams and reduce the impact of operational events. For example, when you set up cross-account observability for Internet Monitor, you can access and view performance and availability measurements generated by monitors in different AWS accounts.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:56:48 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/elasticache-serverless-aws-canada-west-calgary-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">675154f593064d391ea8fb31789cc4cced82b076</guid><title>ElastiCache Serverless is now available in the AWS Canada West (Calgary) region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the availability of Amazon ElastiCache Serverless in the AWS Canada West (Calgary) region. ElastiCache Serverless simplifies cache management and scales to support the most demanding applications. With ElastiCache Serverless, you can create a highly available and scalable cache in less than a minute, eliminating the need to plan for, provision, and manage cache cluster capacity. ElastiCache Serverless automatically stores data redundantly across multiple Availability Zones (AZs) and provides a 99.99% availability &lt;a href="/elasticache/sla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Service Level Agreement (SLA)&lt;/a&gt;. With ElastiCache Serverless, you pay for data stored and compute consumed by your workload, with no upfront commitments or additional costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:27:32 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-elasticache,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-lambda-ruby-3-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6e1cd91ef27dbe660512483fae5ca79c09807f9e</guid><title>AWS Lambda adds support for Ruby 3.3</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Lambda now supports creating serverless applications using Ruby 3.3. Developers can use Ruby 3.3 as both a managed runtime and a container base image, and AWS will automatically apply updates to the managed runtime and base image as they become available.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:53:34 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-lambda,marketing:marchitecture/serverless</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-sagemaker-studio-code-editor-custom-images/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f98f0785c20b8e9d3b2df56e9626847849aded40</guid><title>Amazon SageMaker Studio Code Editor now supports custom images</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are enabling Machine Learning (ML) teams’ using &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/sagemaker/latest/dg/code-editor.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Code Editor&lt;/a&gt;, our SageMaker Studio integrated development environment (IDE) based on Code-OSS (VS Code open source), to use custom built IDE images. With this new feature, you can boost your ML development team’s productivity by providing them with customized development environments that provide the frameworks, libraries and IDE extensions they need, thus reducing their time-to-code.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:29:37 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-sagemaker-studio,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-m6gd-database-instances-additional-aws-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ab265459db4269dd3237ed40f5db55b5b6a62b17</guid><title>Amazon RDS now supports M6gd database instances in six additional AWS regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)&lt;/a&gt; for PostgreSQL, MySQL, and MariaDB now supports AWS Graviton2-based M6gd database instances in Asia Pacific (Hong Kong, Melbourne, Seoul), Canada (Central), Europe (Milan), and Middle East (Bahrain) regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-sagemaker-notebooks-p5-c6i-c7i-m6i-m7i-r6i-r7i-instance-types/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fa5b5693e267c0b1780a39b14b94e87f972d8ce3</guid><title>Amazon SageMaker notebooks now support P5, C6i, C7i, M6i, M7i, R6i, and R7i instance types</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce general availability of Amazon EC2 P5, C6i, C7i, M6i, M7i, R6i, and R7i instances on SageMaker notebooks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:29:07 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-sagemaker,marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-iam-identity-center-europe-spain-asia-pacific-hyderabad-aws-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2c21add3cfb74c7793c502bc6468aa601bdbf977</guid><title>AWS IAM Identity Center is now available in the  Europe (Spain) and Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) AWS Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You can now deploy AWS IAM Identity Center in the Europe (Spain) and Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) AWS Regions. With the addition of these AWS Regions, IAM Identity Center is now available in 32 AWS Regions globally.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:25:40 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-iam-identity-center,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/general-availability-amazon-ec2-g6-instances/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9c1669ee7ed8296cc5b6416a7a235155f81c5f7c</guid><title>Announcing general availability of Amazon EC2 G6 instances</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we are announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 G6 instances powered by NVIDIA L4 Tensor Core GPUs. G6 instances can be used for a wide range of graphics-intensive and machine learning use cases. G6 instances deliver up to 2x higher performance for deep learning inference and graphics workloads compared to Amazon EC2 G4dn instances.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-opensearch-ingestion-streaming-data-geographical-location/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3051ced0d09304528cd2053d9332cff8d366a0fc</guid><title>Amazon OpenSearch Ingestion now supports enrichment of streaming data with geographical location</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon OpenSearch Ingestion now enables you to enrich events with geographical location data from an IP address, allowing you to add additional context to your observability and security data in realtime. Additionally, you can configure mapping templates in Amazon OpenSearch clusters to automatically display these enriched events on a geographical map using OpenSearch Dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-opensearch-service,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-b2b-data-interchange-hipaa-eligible-x12-version-5010-hipaa-transactions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0e8b3d9e1e170dfd517e9e5e001f6fecf8c62701</guid><title>AWS B2B Data Interchange is now HIPAA eligible and supports X12 version 5010 HIPAA transactions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS B2B Data Interchange is now a Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) eligible service and supports X12 version 5010 HIPAA transaction sets, extending the service’s fully automated, event-driven EDI transformation capabilities to healthcare use cases.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:03:14 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-b2b-data-interchange,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-opensearch-service-doubles-storage-or1-four-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d100ac89c75921b0a7c6eddc39f1180524ea7663</guid><title>Amazon OpenSearch Service doubles storage for OR1 and expands to four more regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;OR1, the OpenSearch Optimized Instance family, now doubles the max allowed storage per instance. OR1 also expands availability to four additional regions- Canada Central, EU (London), and Asia Pacific (Hyderabad, Seoul). OR1 delivers up to 30% price-performance improvement over existing instances (based on internal benchmarks), and uses Amazon S3 to provide 11 9s of durability. The new OR1 instances are best suited for indexing-heavy workloads, and offers better indexing performance compared to the existing memory optimized instances available on OpenSearch Service.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-opensearch-service,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-application-migration-service-migration-uefi-servers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">48ac5c703f0120c38498d760918d7dec39e92285</guid><title>AWS Application Migration Service now supports migration of UEFI servers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can use &lt;a href="/application-migration-service/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Application Migration Service&lt;/a&gt; (AWS MGN) to migrate Linux servers with UEFI boot mode.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:04:47 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-application-migration-service,marketing:marchitecture/migration,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-transfer-family-predefined-security-policies-sftp-connectors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9a14f5003db81fff83d654d84b44ebae782a0886</guid><title>AWS Transfer Family offers predefined security policies for SFTP connectors</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/aws-transfer-family/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Transfer Family&lt;/a&gt;’s predefined security policies for SFTP connectors gives you the flexibility to control cryptographic algorithms used for establishing connections with remote SFTP servers, enabling compatibility with a wider range of remote server configurations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 21:58:24 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-transfer-family,marketing:marchitecture/migration</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-datazone-integration-aws-lake-formation-hybrid-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8f323206b998244f7aea34f312a61dc14dfb3aec</guid><title>Amazon DataZone announces integration with AWS Lake Formation hybrid mode</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/datazone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon DataZone&lt;/a&gt; is used by customers to catalog, discover, analyze, share, and govern data at scale across organizational boundaries with governance and access controls. Today, Amazon DataZone has introduced an integration with &lt;a href="/lake-formation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Lake Formation&lt;/a&gt; hybrid mode. This integration enables customers to easily publish and share their &lt;a href="/glue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Glue&lt;/a&gt; tables through Amazon DataZone, without the need to register them in AWS Lake Formation first. Hybrid mode allows customers to start managing permissions on their AWS Glue tables through AWS Lake Formation, while continuing to maintain any existing IAM permissions on these tables.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 20:09:40 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-datazone,general:products/aws-lake-formation</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-cloudwatch-cross-account-anomaly-detection/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0a59671dc6ae257ebfb5dbc6e710d7a6c1834ff2</guid><title>Amazon CloudWatch now supports cross-account anomaly detection</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon CloudWatch now supports Anomaly Detection on metrics shared across your accounts. CloudWatch Anomaly Detection now lets you track unexpected changes in metric behavior across multiple accounts from a single monitoring account through CloudWatch cross-account observability.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:35:18 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-clean-rooms-ml-generally-available/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7b6a37eb9cddea71e5638040e23e804444ceae3e</guid><title>AWS Clean Rooms ML is now generally available</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the general availability of AWS Clean Rooms ML, which helps companies apply machine learning (ML) to generate predictive insights in a data collaboration without sharing their raw data with their partners. This capability launches with an ML model that helps companies create lookalike segments. With AWS Clean Rooms ML lookalike modeling, you can train your own custom model using your data and invite your partners to bring a small sample of their records to a collaboration to generate an expanded set of similar records while protecting the underlying data with purpose-built privacy controls. AWS Clean Rooms ML enables collaborative ML use cases including those for healthcare, financial services, and travel and hospitality.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 19:23:20 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-clean-rooms,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/mistral-large-foundation-model-amazon-bedrock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">95d5b4d4a36519b6510dea961e68275392d47748</guid><title>Mistral Large foundation model now available on Amazon Bedrock</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mistral Large, Mistral AI’s flagship cutting-edge text generation model is now generally available on Amazon Bedrock. Mistral Large is widely known for its top-tier reasoning capabilities, specific instruction following, and multilingual translation abilities. It excels in coding and mathematical tasks and is natively fluent in English, French, Spanish, German, and Italian, with a nuanced understanding of grammar and cultural context. Mistral Large performs well on retrieval augmented generation (RAG) use cases, its 32K token context window facilitates precise information retrieval from lengthy documents.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 18:37:18 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-bedrock-europe-paris-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">589b2f43c2b2b49518ac34d24f9164f6c174e13b</guid><title>Amazon Bedrock is now available in the AWS Europe (Paris) Region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, customers can use Amazon Bedrock in the AWS Europe (Paris) Region to easily build and scale AI applications using a variety of foundation models and generative AI tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:04:02 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-datazone-integration-glue-data-quality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c4199574924906702857f0853cd0953f952cb535</guid><title>Amazon DataZone launches integration with AWS Glue Data Quality</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon DataZone is used by customers to catalog, discover, analyze, share, and govern data at scale across organizational boundaries with governance and access controls. Today, Amazon DataZone launches integration with AWS Glue Data Quality and offers APIs to integrate data quality metrics from third party data quality solutions. This integration helps Amazon DataZone customers gain trust in their data and make confident business decisions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 20:48:45 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-datazone,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-documentdb-middle-east-uae-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d52377a02f35e626da0cb0a6eb1731ff302f7306</guid><title>Amazon DocumentDB is now available in the Middle East (UAE) region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility) is now available in the Middle East (UAE) region adding to the &lt;a href="/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;list of available regions where you can use Amazon DocumentDB&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 21:47:03 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-documentdb,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-marketplace-demo-private-offer-requests-products/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0c3367a318647c88c6ee96ee9300cb349a73cdf0</guid><title>AWS Marketplace now supports demo and private offer requests for products</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Marketplace now gives customers the ability to request product demos and private offers directly from sellers' product listing pages. This helps customers accelerate product evaluations and further reduce their procurement cycle times.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:03:59 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-marketplace,marketing:marchitecture/aws-marketplace-and-partners</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-timestream-liveanalytics-fedramp-high-authorization-aws-govcloud-west-region/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c8ff4443b09d6c306b7178064aa456903e52aba3</guid><title>Amazon Timestream for LiveAnalytics achieves FedRAMP High Authorization in AWS GovCloud (US-West) Region</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can now use Amazon Timestream for LiveAnalytics with workloads that require the FedRAMP High categorization level in the AWS GovCloud (US-West) Region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:56:02 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-timestream,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/elasticache-serverless-aws-govcloud-us-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e4b2366fdfdb271f81a32228728b655a3764f206</guid><title>ElastiCache Serverless is now available in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the availability of Amazon ElastiCache Serverless in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. ElastiCache Serverless simplifies cache management and scales to support the most demanding applications. With ElastiCache Serverless, you can create a highly available and scalable cache in less than a minute, eliminating the need to plan for, provision, and manage cache cluster capacity. ElastiCache Serverless automatically stores data redundantly across multiple Availability Zones (AZs) and provides a 99.99% availability &lt;a href="/elasticache/sla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Service Level Agreement (SLA)&lt;/a&gt;. With ElastiCache Serverless, you pay for data stored and compute consumed by your workload, with no upfront commitments or additional costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:05:08 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-elasticache,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-appsync-increases-service-quota-adds-subscription/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4866e78cf9013409e791fa452fc5a04e303b81ff</guid><title>AWS AppSync increases existing service quota and adds subscription service quotas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS AppSync is a fully managed service that allows customers to connect applications to data and enable real-time experiences with GraphQL APIs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:07:33 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services,general:products/aws-appsync</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/announcing-aws-deadline-cloud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">15b0a058380a3cc963ed2f3ce655de1d3c9b6524</guid><title>Announcing AWS Deadline Cloud</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces AWS Deadline Cloud, a fully managed service that simplifies render management for teams creating 2D and 3D visual assets for films, TV shows, commercials, games, and industrial design. Deadline Cloud makes it easy to build a cloud-based render farm in minutes that scales from zero to thousands of compute instances, without needing to manage infrastructure. Deadline Cloud includes built-in integrations, including Autodesk Arnold, Autodesk Maya, Foundry Nuke, Luxion KeyShot, and SideFX Houdini, and a broad set of customization tools, so you can reduce the time required to build integrations with the team’s preferred software and tailor your render pipeline to your own needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/media-services,general:products/aws-deadline-cloud</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/vpc-traffic-mirroring-seven-additional-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0590fd1355e2ed8d54ad8eaff3ebc8d995be450e</guid><title>VPC Traffic Mirroring is now available in seven additional regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Traffic Mirroring is available in seven new regions, including AWS Asia Pacific (Jakarta), AWS Asia Pacific (Melbourne), AWS Middle East (UAE), AWS Canada West (Calgary), AWS Europe (Spain), AWS Israel (Tel Aviv), and AWS Europe (Zurich).&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:55:13 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-vpc,marketing:marchitecture/networking-and-content-delivery</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-cloudwatch-custom-dashboards-console-mobile-app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fb608dd5e13de84433a0c53d42d83bbe96a245b9</guid><title>AWS Console Mobile Application adds support for CloudWatch custom dashboards</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS customers can now view real-time and historical data visualizations of their critical resource and application metrics in a mobile-friendly format using CloudWatch custom dashboards in the AWS Console Mobile App. Now AWS customers have convenient access to customized views of their resource and application's health and performance metrics while on-the-go.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,general:products/aws-console-mobile-application,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/chef-11-18-recipes-windows-aws-systems-manager/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0e6d6e9e2768e2ff79d5b8704f08d6962b4a98c5</guid><title>Run Chef 11-18 recipes on Windows using AWS Systems Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="/systems-manager/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;AWS Systems Manager&lt;/a&gt; introduces the ability to run Chef 11-18 recipes on Windows Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) and on-premises instances. These capabilities, previously available only to Linux instances, enable customers to combine the power of Chef recipes with the control and safety benefits from AWS Systems Manager, regardless of whether their instances are running on Linux or Windows operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-systems-manager,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-aurora-zero-etl-integration-redshift-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54ba1b7b6093d56aab766861d963f69a9260ee13</guid><title>Amazon Aurora zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift now in additional regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Aurora MySQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift is now supported in 11 additional regions, enabling near real-time analytics and machine learning (ML) using Amazon Redshift. Based on your analytics needs, you can include or exclude specific databases and tables from an existing or a new zero-ETL integration and selectively bring data into Amazon Redshift.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:04:41 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-aurora,general:products/amazon-redshift,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/knowledge-bases-amazon-bedrock-private-network-policies-opensearch-serverless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23480e79491f4a5d0e0055ff6b88d6ee40934075</guid><title>Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports private network policies for OpenSearch Serverless</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) capability that allows you to connect foundation models (FMs) to internal company data sources to deliver more relevant, context-specific, and accurate responses. We are excited to announce that Knowledge Bases now supports private network policies for &lt;a href="/opensearch-service/features/serverless/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon OpenSearch Serverless (OSS)&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:53:55 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-bedrock</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-appstream-2-0-idp-initiated-sessions-windows-client/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26ee082244b31a5d0a5a21d4823f495b0ffae7f8</guid><title>Amazon AppStream 2.0 can now launch IdP-initiated sessions using the Windows client</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon AppStream 2.0 now supports launching the client application for Windows from an Identity Provider (IdP)-initiated SAML 2.0 sign-in flow. This feature allows your end-users to sign in to SAML 2.0 IdPs using their system's default web browser before transitioning into the streaming session in the Windows client.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:22:35 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-appstream-2-0,marketing:marchitecture/desktop-and-app-streaming,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/partner-analytics-now-analytics-insights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a4aaf1ea480e4fab68faf3dc19e5181be115e066</guid><title>Partner Analytics is now Analytics and Insights</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The AWS Partner Analytics Dashboard is now known as Analytics and Insights, covering more insights for your AWS Marketplace and APN businesses than ever. We’ve streamlined the interface and added several new features to help you better understand how to grow with AWS:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ol&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;The new Training and Certifications tab gives you self-service access to commonly requested data on your teams’ Training and Certification achievements. These insights help you better understand your teams' strengths and identify areas needing training investment to better serve customers.&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;We expanded the Solution Provider and Distributor tab to also highlight opportunity and AWS account details for Public Sector, Partner-Originated, and Partner Growth Discounts.&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;New ACE Co-Sell features are now integrated into the Opportunities tab to help you better understand and manage your pipeline.&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ol&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:05:28 +0000</pubDate><category>marketing:marchitecture/aws-marketplace-and-partners,marketing:marchitecture/partner-network</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/aws-resilience-hub-fsx-windows-trust-advisor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">50c587ee6360daf31021cd7ae83439ecbbbef559</guid><title>AWS Resilience Hub expands support for FSx for Windows and Trust Advisor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Resilience Hub has expanded support for AWS Trusted Advisor, adding an additional check for unrecoverable application components. In addition, Resilience Hub has expanded support to assess applications that include Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Resilience Hub provides a single place to define, validate, and track the resilience of your applications so that you can avoid unnecessary downtime caused by software, infrastructure, or operational disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-resilience-hub,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-emr-ec2-gracefully-replaces-unhealthy-core-nodes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4b9417e6234a0208d1013970063accec737d985c</guid><title>Amazon EMR on EC2 now gracefully replaces unhealthy core nodes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to introduce a new &lt;a href="/emr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon EMR&lt;/a&gt; on EC2 feature that enables automatic graceful replacement of unhealthy core nodes to ensure continued optimal cluster operations and prevent data loss. Additionally, EMR on EC2 will publish CloudWatch events to provide visibility into node health and recovery actions. These improvements are available for all Amazon EMR releases.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:10:13 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-emr,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-transcribe-spanish-language-pii-identification-redaction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">662608baf4b0a91fd2a57cdd0522b52379a3d85b</guid><title>Amazon Transcribe launches Spanish language support for PII identification and redaction</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are excited to announce Amazon Transcribe’s support for Personally Identifiable Information (PII) identification and redaction for Spanish (US) audio transcription, in addition to the existing support for English audio. Amazon Transcribe uses state-of-the-art machine learning technology to help identify sensitive information such as Social Security number, credit card/bank account information, and contact information (i.e. name, email address, phone number and mailing address).&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 18:55:19 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-transcribe,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/private-access-aws-management-console-commercial-regions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24404d2926357ebb1c63399c19256ca2df3064d6</guid><title>Private Access to the AWS Management Console is now available in all commercial AWS Regions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can now deploy AWS Management Console Private Access in US West (N. California), Africa (Cape Town), Asia Pacific (Hong Kong), Asia Pacific (Jakarta), Asia Pacific (Melbourne), Asia Pacific (Osaka), Canada (West), Europe (Frankfurt), Europe (Stockholm), Europe (Paris), Europe (Spain), Europe (Milan), Europe (Zurich), Middle East (Bahrain), Middle East (UAE), and South America (São Paulo). With this launch, AWS Management Console Private Access is now available in all commercial AWS Regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:24:34 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/aws-management-console,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item><item><link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/04/amazon-rds-sql-server-single-az-read-replica/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7617c821366d33c18207bc20eb77f6efd662a8b1</guid><title>Amazon RDS for SQL Server supports Single-AZ Read Replica</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/rds/sqlserver/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Amazon RDS for SQL Server&lt;/a&gt; now supports Single-AZ Read-Replicas using Always On Availability Groups (AOAG) for Enterprise Edition. This provides customer the option to create up to 15 number of read replicas from a Single-AZ Enterprise Edition source instance in the same region, or cross regions. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 19:04:56 +0000</pubDate><category>general:products/amazon-rds,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category><author>aws@amazon.com</author></item></channel></rss>